Well, what else can we do?
好了，现在我们还可以做些什么
Well, we can wait for a certain number of blocks for our contract finish with
我们可以等待一定数量的区块，直到我们的合约完成
so we've deployed the contract.
现在我们已经部署好了合约
But maybe we want to wait one block to make sure it actually gets attached to the chain.
但我们也可能会想要等待一个区块以确保它确实已经上链了
So we can say
所以我们可以写
const.Deployment received equals await, contract dot deploy transaction dot Wait,
"const deploymentReceipt = await contract.deployTransaction.wait()"
and specify the number of confirmations that we want to actually wait.
并且需要指定我们想要等待确认的确切数量
So we'll wait one block confirmation to make sure that this happened.
所以我们将等待一个区块确认以确保该做的都做好了
And then we can do console dot log,
然后我们可以 "console.log()"
this deployment receipt option.
里面填上这个 "deploymentReceipt" 选项
So if we run the code now, we can see all this information about our transaction,
如果我们现在运行代码，可以看到有关我们交易的所有信息
and we can see exactly what our transaction looks like,
可以精确地看到我们的交易是什么样的
we can see there's two is no because we're creating a contract
可以看到 "to" 是 "null" 因为我们是在创建合约
from is going to be this ganache address that we got the private key for,
"from" 是我们使用的那个私钥所对应的 Ganache 地址
we see the contract address that we created
"contractAddress" 就是我们创建的这个合约
transaction index, we can see gas use gas use log bloom block hash transaction,
还有 "transactionIndex", "gasUsed", "logsBloom", "blockHash", "transactionHash"
and we can see all this information about our transaction,
总之我们能看到有关我们交易的所有信息
something I want you to take note of is the deployment receipt and the deployment transaction,
我想让你注意的是这个 "deploymentReceipt" 以及 "deployTransaction"
I want you to separate these two because it's going to make your life a lot easier.
我希望你能把这两个东西区分开，这样可以让你舒服很多
So we're going to do quick console dot log,
我们来快速处理一下 "console.log"
here is the deployment transaction.
"Here is the deployment transaction: "
And then we'll do console dot log
接着是 "console.log"
contract, dot deploy transaction.
"contract.deployTransaction"
And then I'm going to copy this whole line by just typing Command C or Ctrl. C right there.
然后我要复制这一整行，使用 "Command C" 或是 "Ctrl C"
And then here is the deployment. Here is the transaction receipt.
这里把 "Here is the deployment" 改成 "Here is the transaction receipt"
And then this deployment is receipt is the transaction receipt.
这里写的是 "deploymentReceipt" 而这里是 "transaction receipt"
So I'm just going to rename this to transaction receipt.
所以我要把这里重命名成 "transactionReceipt"
To make it a little bit clearer, which ones which,
为了让它更清晰，哪个是哪个
and we'll run this one more time.
我们再运行一次
You only get a transaction receipt, when you wait for a block confirmation.
你只有在等待区块确认时才能获得交易回执("transaction receipt")
Otherwise, you're gonna get the contract object, which has the deploy transaction with it,
否则，你得到的就只有合约对象，以及它包含的部署交易("deploy transaction")信息
this distinction will be more important later on.
这种差异之后才会显得比较重要
But I wanted you to know what the difference between the two
但我现在就想让你们知道这二者的区别
transaction receipt is what you get when you wait for a block confirmation,
交易回执是你等待区块确认时获得的
the deployment transaction or the transaction response, transaction response
而部署交易或者说是交易响应("transaction response")
is what you get just when you create your transaction.
则是在你创建交易时获得的
So transaction receipts transactional response, they're different
所以这个是交易回执，这个是交易响应，它们是不同的
receipt is what you get when you wait for a transaction to finish.
回执是你的等待交易完成时获得的东西
And then response is just what you initially get.
而响应则是你一开始就会获得东西
Make sense? Okay, great.
讲清楚了吧？OK 很好
We're gonna go ahead and delete those.
我们要把这些东西删掉
But those lines will be in the code associated with the GitHub.
不过它们仍然会在课程关联的 GitHub 中显示出来